https://www.sukup.com/privacy

Privacy Policy & CookiesLast Updated: January 30, 2020Your privacy is important to Sukup Manufacturing. Our Privacy Policy covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.Collection and Use of Personal InformationPersonal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Sukup. Sukup may share this personal information within the company and with your consent may be shared on our webpage and social media platforms. Sukup may also combine collected personal information with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.What personal information we collectWhen you participate in an online survey, provide a testimonial, send an inquiry, or submit your project to Sukup, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, e-mail address, and contact preferences.How we use your personal informationThe personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on the latest Sukup product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. It also helps us to improve our services, content, and advertising.We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Sukup products, services, and customer communications.If you enter a contest, enter a promotional event, provide a testimonial, or submit a project we may use the information you provide to administer related programs and with your consent may share such information on our webpage and social media platforms. All data shared on social media platforms do not fall under this privacy policy. For further information see the section below entitled Links to Unaffiliated Third Party Websites.Protection of Personal InformationSukup takes precautions - including administrative, technical, and physical measures - to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.When you use Sukup products, services, or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address on a social networking site, that information is public. Please take care when using these features. Sukup is not responsible or liable for the information shared in these instances. Personal Information shared on social media platforms, on third party websites, or outside of the Sukup website do not fall under this privacy policy. For further information see the section below entitled Links to Unaffiliated Third Party Websites.Managing or Deleting My Personal InformationWe store your data until it is no longer necessary provide our services. This determination is made on a case-by-case basis that depends on things like the nature of the data, why it is collected and processed, relevant legal or operational retention needs, and consent given by person sharing data.To remove all known information about you from Sukup websites, please email privacy@sukup.com, call 641-892-4222 or send via mail to Sukup Manufacturing Co., ATTN: Legal Department, P.O. Box 677, Sheffield, IA 50475. We will need to collect data to process such request, but upon processing, we will delete all collected personal information we have saved, unless require to maintain by law.You may at any time choose to stop receiving Sukup's emails relating to our marketing materials by following the unsubscribing instructions contained in the emails we send you. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to privacy@sukup.com and requesting the removal of your name from Sukup marketing lists.Collection and Use of Non-Personal InformationWe may also collect non-personal information - data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following areas are examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it: We may collect information such as language, zip code, area code, location, and the time zone where a Sukup product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising.Links to Unaffiliated Third Party WebsitesThis Site may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. If you link to or otherwise visit any other websites managed by third parties, Sukup encourages you to review the privacy policies available on such websites. You understand that Sukup Manufacturing Co. has no control over those websites and is not responsible or liable for the policies and practices followed by such third parties.ChildrenWe do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.Revisions and Contact InformationWe periodically update the features of Sukup Websites. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without advance notice and any modifications are effective when they are posted here. The date of the newest version will be posted on top of this page. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personal information at this Site, to see if the Privacy Policy has changed. If you have any questions, please contact us by sending an e-mail message to privacy@sukup.com with the subject line heading of "Privacy Policy Request."Privacy QuestionsIf you have questions or concerns about the Sukup Privacy Policy, please email privacy@sukup.com, call 641-892-4222 or send via mail to Sukup Manufacturing Co., ATTN: Legal Department, P.O. Box 677, Sheffield, IA 50475.CookiesWhat are cookies?Cookies are a small amount of data generated by a website and downloaded to your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. They are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to any other visited website that recognizes that cookie.The most common use is to store a user's session after logging into a website. Some cookies are used by some websites to store items places in a shopping cart. Other cookies allow you to navigate between pages efficiently and generally improving your user experience. Many cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often.For further information on cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit http://allaboutcookies.orgSukup websites may use cookies to distinguish you from other users. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our websites and also allows us to improve our sites. By using this Site, www.sukup.com, or any other Sukup Website, you accept the use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.Which cookies do we use?1. Essential Cookies. These cookies are necessary in order to enable you to navigate around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure area of the website. This category of cookies cannot be disabled. We may use the following cookies:
Cookie Name Description Website
CraftSessionId SetCraft relies on PHP sessions to maintain sessions across web requests. That is done via the PHP session cookie. Craft names that cookie “CraftSessionId” by default, but it can be renamed via the phpSessionId config setting. This cookie will expire as soon as the session expires. www.sukup.com
*_identity AuthenticationWhen you log into the Control Panel, you will get an authentication cookie used to maintain your authenticated state. The cookie name is prefixed with a long, randomly generated string, followed by _identity. The cookie only stores information necessary to maintain a secure, authenticated session and will only exist for as long as the user is authenticated in Craft. www.sukup.com
*_username If you check the "Keep me logged in" option during login, this cookie is used to remember the username for your next authentication. www.sukup.com
CRAFT_CSRF_TOKEN Protects us and you as a user against Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks. www.sukup.com
ASP.NET_SessionId Set a unique ID identifying the user session. dealer.sukup.com
.ASPXAUTH Authentication cookie used when a user signs in to dealer.sukup.com dealer.sukup.com
cookieconsent_status Enables the use of cookies notification dealer.sukup.com 2. Analytics Cookies. These cookies collect information about how you use a website, for instance which pages you go to most often, what searches you perform, and whether you receive error messages from the visited web pages.Our website uses Google Analytics Cookies. Information collected by the Google Analytics cookies will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States of America and anywhere else they may be located in accordance with its privacy practices. To see an overview of privacy at Google and how this applies to Google Analytics, visit http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html. You may opt out of Google Analytics’ tracking by visiting https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Our website may use the following Google Analytics Cookies and other Analytic Cookies:
Cookie Name Description Website
lang, metrics_token, personalization_id, tfw_exp Enables Twitter feed www.sukup.com
uvc Allows social sharing with AddToAny www.sukup.com
Google Analytics: _utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmt, _utmz Enables analytics dealer.sukup.com
Google Analytics: _ga, _gid, _gat* Enables analytics www.SafeTHome.com 3. Other Cookies. Besides the cookies we had previously mentioned, the cookies listed below may also be set during your visit due to our use of third party vendor, such as YouTube, Facebook, and DoubleClick. These cookies record your visit to our site and are typically used to recognize you when you return to our website, enable widgets to work correctly and may provide relevant content based on the pages you have visited and the links you have followed.
Cookie Name Description
YouTube Enables videos, widget
Facebook Enables social media, widget
DoubleClick Enables ad, tracker How to control and delete cookies through the browserThe ability to manage or delete cookies can be done within an internet browser. In order to do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “Help”, “Tools” or “Edit” facility). Please visit the following links to learn more about cookies management in most commonly used browsers:Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=enFireFox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/products/firefox/protect-your-privacy/cookiesInternet Explorer (IE): https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookieswww.sukup.comdealer.sukup.comwww.SafeTHome.comCookies that have been set in the pastIf you have disabled one or more cookies, we may still use information collected from cookies prior to your disabled preference being set, however, we will stop using the disabled cookie to collect any further information.Third Parties CookiesPlease note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical, performance cookies, or targeting cookiesYou block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access our website at all or certain parts of it.Sukup Websites:www.sukup.comdealer.sukup.comwww.safethome.com
ARE YOU READY TO START A PROJECT?
Find Your Dealer
Necessary (Required)
Cookies that the site cannot function properly without. This includes cookies for access to secure areas and CSRF security. Please note that Craft’s default cookies do not collect any personal or sensitive information. Craft's default cookies do not collect IP addresses. The information they store is not sent to Pixel & Tonic or any 3rd parties.
Name: CraftSessionId
Description: Craft relies on PHP sessions to maintain sessions across web requests. That is done via the PHP session cookie. Craft names that cookie “CraftSessionId” by default, but it can be renamed via the phpSessionId config setting. This cookie will expire as soon as the session expires.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Session
Name: *_identity
Description: When you log into the Control Panel, you will get an authentication cookie used to maintain your authenticated state. The cookie name is prefixed with a long, randomly generated string, followed by _identity. The cookie only stores information necessary to maintain a secure, authenticated session and will only exist for as long as the user is authenticated in Craft.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Persistent
Name: *_username
Description: If you check the "Keep me logged in" option during login, this cookie is used to remember the username for your next authentication.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Persistent
Name: CRAFT_CSRF_TOKEN
Description: Protects us and you as a user against Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks.
Provider: this site
Expiry: Session
Statistics
Statistic cookies help us understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
Social
Cookies that are set from social networks.
Name: lang
Description:
Provider: Twitter
Expiry:
Name: metrics_token
Description:
Provider: Twitter
Expiry:
Name: personalization_id
Description:
Provider: Twitter
Expiry:
Name: tfw_exp
Description:
Provider: Twitter
Expiry:
Name: uvc
Description:
Provider: AddToAny
Expiry:
Details
Hide Details
COOKIES
